{"vongolaedison@gmail.com": {"email": "vongolaedison@gmail.com", "first_name": "Edison", "last_name": "Liang", "age": 20, "gender": "m", "sexuality": "f", "up_to_category": 5, "up_to_question": 0, "category_weights": {"personality": 5, "morals": 5, "politics": 4, "interest_hobbies": 5, "life_goals": 5, "love_languages": 5}, "questions": [{"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "Rank your ideal retirement plan", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udfe0 Suburban House": 10}, {"\u2615 Opening your own cafe": 7.5}, {"\ud83e\uddd1 Living off the land": 5}, {"\ud83c\udfd9\ufe0f City Apartment": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "Rank your future family preferences", "answers": [{"\ud83d\udc76 Kids are a must": 10}, {"\ud83d\udc36 Fur babies only": 7.5}, {"\ud83d\udeab Just us, no kids or pets": 5}, {"\ud83e\udd14 Still figuring it out": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": false, "is_similar_question": false, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How locked is your ideal partner?", "answers": [{"How locked is your ideal partner?": 5}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "BINARY", "question_text": "Which of these are you?", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udf1e Early bird": 0}, {"\ud83c\udf19 Night owl": 1}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "BINARY", "question_text": "How clean do you keep your space?", "answers": [{"\u2728 Spotless": 0}, {"\ud83c\udf00 Organised chaos": 0}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "On the weekend you're more likely to?", "answers": [{"\ud83d\ude34 Sleeping in & doing nothing": 10}, {"\u2705 Being productive & crossing off tasks": 7.5}, {"\ud83c\udfb2 Random spontaneous plans": 5}, {"\ud83c\udfad Going out & having fun": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "On a date you're more likely to?", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udf33 A scenic walk in the park": 10}, {"\ud83c\udf7d\ufe0f Dinner at a cozy restaurant": 7.5}, {"\ud83c\udfb3 A fun activity (e.g., mini-golf, bowling)": 5}, {"\u2615 Coffee at a cute caf\u00e9": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "On a scale of 1 to 5, how often do you exercise?", "answers": [{"On a scale of 1 to 5, how often do you exercise?": 3}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "On a scale of 1 to 5, how much do you love traveling?", "answers": [{"On a scale of 1 to 5, how much do you love traveling?": 4}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How important is it that your partner has a similar lifestyle to you?", "answers": [{"How important is it that your partner has a similar lifestyle to you?": 3}]}, {"category_name": "politics", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "I think wealth should be shared equally like giant pizza slices - no one should get all yummy bits while others are left with just the crust", "answers": [{"I think wealth should be shared equally like giant pizza slices - no one should get all yummy bits while others are left with just the crust": 4}]}, {"category_name": "politics", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "I think the free economy will always correct itself without any government help - its like magic!", "answers": [{"I think the free economy will always correct itself without any government help - its like magic!": 4}]}, {"category_name": "politics", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "In think in turbulent times, a decisive government that may restrict some personal freedoms is necessary to keep society on track", "answers": [{"In think in turbulent times, a decisive government that may restrict some personal freedoms is necessary to keep society on track": 5}]}, {"category_name": "politics", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "I think preserving individual freedom and free speech is more important - even if that means quite a bit of societal chaos", "answers": [{"I think preserving individual freedom and free speech is more important - even if that means quite a bit of societal chaos": 3}]}, {"category_name": "politics", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How important is it that your partner has a similar political view to you?", "answers": [{"How important is it that your partner has a similar political view to you?": 5}]}, {"category_name": "interests_hobbies", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "BINARY", "question_text": "Are you into video games?", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udfae Yes, I love gaming!": 1}, {"\ud83c\udf19 No, not my thing": 0}]}, {"category_name": "interests_hobbies", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "BINARY", "question_text": "Do you prefer solo hobbies over group activities?", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udfa8 Yes, I enjoy hobbies alone.": 0}, {"\ud83e\udd38\u200d\u2642\ufe0f No, I love group activities!": 1}]}, {"category_name": "interests_hobbies", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "On your free day you're most likely to?", "answers": [{"\ud83d\udcfa Binge-watch a new show": 10}, {"\ud83c\udfcb\ufe0f\u200d\u2642\ufe0f Hit the gym or go for a hike": 7.5}, {"\ud83d\udcd6 Read a book or listen to a podcast": 5}, {"\ud83d\ude80 Go out and explore the city": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "interests_hobbies", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "Rank your dream vacation", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udfdd Chilling on a beach": 10}, {"\ud83c\udff0 Exploring historical sites": 7.5}, {"\ud83c\udfd4 Going on an outdoor adventure": 5}, {"\ud83c\udfd9 Partying in a big city": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "interests_hobbies", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "On a scale of 1 to 5, how much do you love trying new hobbies?", "answers": [{"On a scale of 1 to 5, how much do you love trying new hobbies?": 5}]}, {"category_name": "interests_hobbies", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How important is it that your partner has similar hobbies and interests to you?", "answers": [{"How important is it that your partner has similar hobbies and interests to you?": 5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "Rank your ideal retirement plan", "answers": [{"\ud83e\uddd1 Living off the land": 10}, {"\u2615 Opening your own cafe": 7.5}, {"\ud83c\udfe0 Suburban House": 5}, {"\ud83c\udfd9\ufe0f City Apartment": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "Rank your future family preferences", "answers": [{"\ud83d\udc76 Kids are a must": 10}, {"\ud83d\udeab Just us, no kids or pets": 7.5}, {"\ud83d\udc36 Fur babies only": 5}, {"\ud83e\udd14 Still figuring it out": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "Rank in order of how you prioritise your financial goals", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udfe6 Saving & investing for the future": 10}, {"\u2708\ufe0f Spending on experiences (travel, events)": 7.5}, {"\ud83e\udd11 Living in the moment, enjoying life": 5}, {"\ud83d\udcb0 Prioritizing security (buying a home)": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": false, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How locked in are you?", "answers": [{"How locked in are you?": 4}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": false, "is_similar_question": false, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How locked is your ideal partner?", "answers": [{"How locked is your ideal partner?": 3}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How important is it that your partner has similar life goals to you?", "answers": [{"How important is it that your partner has similar life goals to you?": 5}]}]}, "femaleanto@gmail.com": {"email": "femaleanto@gmail.com", "first_name": "edinas", "last_name": "dsnadf", "age": 24, "gender": "f", "sexuality": "m", "up_to_category": 5, "up_to_question": 0, "category_weights": {"personality": 5, "morals": 5, "politics": 5, "interest_hobbies": 5, "life_goals": 5, "love_languages": 5}, "questions": [{"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "Rank your ideal retirement plan", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udfe0 Suburban House": 10}, {"\ud83e\uddd1 Living off the land": 7.5}, {"\u2615 Opening your own cafe": 5}, {"\ud83c\udfd9\ufe0f City Apartment": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "Rank your future family preferences", "answers": [{"\ud83d\udc36 Fur babies only": 10}, {"\ud83d\udc76 Kids are a must": 7.5}, {"\ud83d\udeab Just us, no kids or pets": 5}, {"\ud83e\udd14 Still figuring it out": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": false, "is_similar_question": false, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How locked is your ideal partner?", "answers": [{"How locked is your ideal partner?": 5}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "BINARY", "question_text": "Which of these are you?", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udf1e Early bird": 0}, {"\ud83c\udf19 Night owl": 1}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "BINARY", "question_text": "How clean do you keep your space?", "answers": [{"\u2728 Spotless": 0}, {"\ud83c\udf00 Organised chaos": 1}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "On the weekend you're more likely to?", "answers": [{"\ud83d\ude34 Sleeping in & doing nothing": 10}, {"\u2705 Being productive & crossing off tasks": 7.5}, {"\ud83c\udfad Going out & having fun": 5}, {"\ud83c\udfb2 Random spontaneous plans": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "On a date you're more likely to?", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udf7d\ufe0f Dinner at a cozy restaurant": 10}, {"\ud83c\udfb3 A fun activity (e.g., mini-golf, bowling)": 7.5}, {"\u2615 Coffee at a cute caf\u00e9": 5}, {"\ud83c\udf33 A scenic walk in the park": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "On a scale of 1 to 5, how often do you exercise?", "answers": [{"On a scale of 1 to 5, how often do you exercise?": 5}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "On a scale of 1 to 5, how much do you love traveling?", "answers": [{"On a scale of 1 to 5, how much do you love traveling?": 5}]}, {"category_name": "lifestyle", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How important is it that your partner has a similar lifestyle to you?", "answers": [{"How important is it that your partner has a similar lifestyle to you?": 5}]}, {"category_name": "politics", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "I think wealth should be shared equally like giant pizza slices - no one should get all yummy bits while others are left with just the crust", "answers": [{"I think wealth should be shared equally like giant pizza slices - no one should get all yummy bits while others are left with just the crust": 5}]}, {"category_name": "politics", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "I think the free economy will always correct itself without any government help - its like magic!", "answers": [{"I think the free economy will always correct itself without any government help - its like magic!": 5}]}, {"category_name": "politics", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "In think in turbulent times, a decisive government that may restrict some personal freedoms is necessary to keep society on track", "answers": [{"In think in turbulent times, a decisive government that may restrict some personal freedoms is necessary to keep society on track": 5}]}, {"category_name": "politics", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "I think preserving individual freedom and free speech is more important - even if that means quite a bit of societal chaos", "answers": [{"I think preserving individual freedom and free speech is more important - even if that means quite a bit of societal chaos": 5}]}, {"category_name": "politics", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How important is it that your partner has a similar political view to you?", "answers": [{"How important is it that your partner has a similar political view to you?": 5}]}, {"category_name": "interests_hobbies", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "BINARY", "question_text": "Are you into video games?", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udfae Yes, I love gaming!": 0}, {"\ud83c\udf19 No, not my thing": 1}]}, {"category_name": "interests_hobbies", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "BINARY", "question_text": "Do you prefer solo hobbies over group activities?", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udfa8 Yes, I enjoy hobbies alone.": 0}, {"\ud83e\udd38\u200d\u2642\ufe0f No, I love group activities!": 1}]}, {"category_name": "interests_hobbies", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "On your free day you're most likely to?", "answers": [{"\ud83d\udcfa Binge-watch a new show": 10}, {"\ud83c\udfcb\ufe0f\u200d\u2642\ufe0f Hit the gym or go for a hike": 7.5}, {"\ud83d\udcd6 Read a book or listen to a podcast": 5}, {"\ud83d\ude80 Go out and explore the city": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "interests_hobbies", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "Rank your dream vacation", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udfdd Chilling on a beach": 10}, {"\ud83c\udff0 Exploring historical sites": 7.5}, {"\ud83c\udfd4 Going on an outdoor adventure": 5}, {"\ud83c\udfd9 Partying in a big city": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "interests_hobbies", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "On a scale of 1 to 5, how much do you love trying new hobbies?", "answers": [{"On a scale of 1 to 5, how much do you love trying new hobbies?": 5}]}, {"category_name": "interests_hobbies", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How important is it that your partner has similar hobbies and interests to you?", "answers": [{"How important is it that your partner has similar hobbies and interests to you?": 5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "Rank your ideal retirement plan", "answers": [{"\ud83e\uddd1 Living off the land": 10}, {"\ud83c\udfe0 Suburban House": 7.5}, {"\u2615 Opening your own cafe": 5}, {"\ud83c\udfd9\ufe0f City Apartment": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "Rank your future family preferences", "answers": [{"\ud83d\udc76 Kids are a must": 10}, {"\ud83d\udc36 Fur babies only": 7.5}, {"\ud83d\udeab Just us, no kids or pets": 5}, {"\ud83e\udd14 Still figuring it out": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "RANKED", "question_text": "Rank in order of how you prioritise your financial goals", "answers": [{"\ud83c\udfe6 Saving & investing for the future": 10}, {"\u2708\ufe0f Spending on experiences (travel, events)": 7.5}, {"\ud83e\udd11 Living in the moment, enjoying life": 5}, {"\ud83d\udcb0 Prioritizing security (buying a home)": 2.5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": false, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How locked in are you?", "answers": [{"How locked in are you?": 5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": false, "is_similar_question": false, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How locked is your ideal partner?", "answers": [{"How locked is your ideal partner?": 5}]}, {"category_name": "life_goals", "is_self_question": true, "is_similar_question": true, "question_type": "SCALE", "question_text": "How important is it that your partner has similar life goals to you?", "answers": [{"How important is it that your partner has similar life goals to you?": 5}]}]}}